Guide to the Verse Records 1984-2008
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Journal Issues
  - Volume 20:2-3, The Prose Issue II, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Volume 20:2-3, The Prose Issue II, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Volume 20:2-3, The Prose Issue II, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Volume 21:1-3, 20th Anniversary Issue, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Volume 21:1-3, 20th Anniversary Issue, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Volume 21:1-3, 20th Anniversary Issue, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Volume 21:1-3, 20th Anniversary Issue, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Volume 21:1-3, 20th Anniversary Issue, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Volume 21:1-3, 20th Anniversary Issue, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Volume 21:1-3, 20th Anniversary Issue, 2004 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Volume 22:1, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Volume 22:1, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Volume 22:2-3, The Sequence (I), 2006 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Volume 22:2-3, The Sequence (I), 2006 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Volume 23:1-3, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Volume 23:1-3, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Volume 24:1-3, French Poetry and Poetics, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Volume 24:1-3, French Poetry and Poetics, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Volume 24:1-3, French Poetry and Poetics, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Volume 24:1-3, French Poetry and Poetics, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Volume 24:1-3, French Poetry and Poetics, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Volume 25:1-3, The Sequence (II), 2006 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Volume 25:1-3, The Sequence (II), 2006 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Series IV: Restricted
  - Verse Books, Wave Press Purchase Agreement, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 1)